I think one of the biggest benefits to being a conservative is having liberals on your side.
Absolutely. Because they're going to cold order. That is what liberals are about. They're more concerned.
And that's what Dr. King talks about in his book, Where Do We Go From Here? Community or Chaos.
He says, you know, liberals are more concerned with order than progress.
Yeah, because at the end of the day, the performance of like being on the right side of history, you know, that's like a big thing with people.
Is that when the history books, when they tell the story, I'm going to be on the right side of history.
But like their right side of history is still like maintaining white supremacy.
Absolutely. Yeah.
Because when they think about that, when they talk about that, I'm just like, well, what are you are you expecting to be writing the books?
Oh, absolutely. Because if that's the case, we're still.
They want to be the authors.
Right. They want to be the authors.
Well, and then I also look at people like Dean Withers as controlled opposition, like, oh, the y'all are buddy, buddy.
Y'all are just more of the y'all are more of the same.
This is a this is like great value Democrats and Republicans.
They just like buddies behind the scene.
Let's let's debate on camera for views and clicks.
I feel like the thing with being like the Dean Withers kid is like, damn, I just watched my bag.
I didn't see that coming.
You'll fix me with that one.
Damn.
Damn, that's crazy.
That's crazy.
That's like seeing that's like somebody calling you like, damn, they pulled the car over with all the bricks in it.
Like, damn, we're going to fuck the streets up with them bricks.
But I got to get a job.
I got to get a job.